(Bernadette:)It's been wonderful, Sheldon,
thanks for asking.
(Bernadette:)Oh, please stop
crying, I'm begging you!
I don't know what else to do!
(Bernadette:)My boobs are empty.
Do you want lasagna?
(Bernadette:)Shh, shh, shh,
it's okay, it's okay.
(Bernadette:)Shh.
(Bernadette:)What have we done?
(Howard:)Hey, I found superhero
baby wipes,
(Howard:)the perfect way
to clean up crime...
(Howard:)and tushies.
(Sheldon:)Ugh.
(Bernadette:)It took me two hours
to get her down.
Oh, you-you relax,
I'll take this shift.
(Raj:)You know, in India when
my baby brother cried like that,
(Raj:)the servants would
just take him far away
(Raj:)so we couldn't hear it.
(Raj:)Not always,
sometimes we'd leave.